// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who has been kicking ass on team-based competitive RPG tournaments?', 
      a: 'Phillip', 
      b: 'Geoff',
      c: 'Autumn',
      d: 'Catherine',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which two have picked up meditation?', 
      a: 'Nick and Josh', 
      b: 'James and Autumn',
      c: 'Darice and Marcus',
      d: 'Andrew and Mercan',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is getting fancy with cross-stitching and embroidery?', 
      a: 'Jalalalala', 
      b: 'Archana',
      c: 'Catherine',
      d: 'Haley',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been dominating at ping pong every day?', 
      a: 'Melissa', 
      b: 'Gillian',
      c: 'Archana',
      d: 'West',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who ate a pint of Blue Bell every day for a week?', 
      a: 'West', 
      b: 'BDF',
      c: 'Sarah',
      d: 'Becky',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been getting savvy with investing?', 
      a: 'Kellee', 
      b: 'Adam',
      c: 'Tomi',
      d: 'Jane',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who can do a 5k in 28 minutes now?', 
      a: 'Tyler', 
      b: 'Tomi',
      c: 'Matt',
      d: 'Perica',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been saving a shit ton of cash by taking on all their own house repairs and remodeling?', 
      a: 'Jenn', 
      b: 'Lynn',
      c: 'Cahak',
      d: 'West',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who is ready to wow us with a new card trick called the Triumph?', 
      a: 'JoCo', 
      b: 'Jlowe',
      c: 'Tyler',
      d: 'Anjali',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who skydived because they missed flying?', 
      a: 'Gillian', 
      b: 'Crystal',
      c: 'Chelsea',
      d: 'Lauren',
      answer: 'a'
    }
  ]
};